Guide to the Christian Conference of Asia Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Program Areas / Activities, Series IV
  - Education Desk
    - Programme
      - Asian Ecumenical Educational Exchange (AEEE)
        - Scholarship applications and correspondence
          - Marie Divinagracia, 1979-1980 (Box 9, Folder 10)
          - Rebecca Doraipandian, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 22)
          - Silas Ekka, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 26)
          - Djoko Ekoharsono, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 28)
          - Ronald Elder, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 24)
          - William Christopher Embathy, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 16)
          - Limuel R. Equina, 1991-1993 (Box 9, Folder 8)
          - Fineaso Faalafi, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 34)
          - Kalyanie Gamalatge, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 1)
          - Ciriaco Ganchorre, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 25)
          - Usha Gangadharan, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 32)
          - Yang Hyun Hae, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
          - Charles Illuri, 1982-1986 (Box 21, Folder 17)
          - S.A. William Joseph, 1985-1986 (Box 21, Folder 18)
          - Margaret Kalaielvi, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
          - A. Kamalaseharan, 1986-1988 (Box 21, Folder 19)
          - Neelakandar Kandasamy, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 20)
          - Henry Karunakaran, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 38)
          - Kim Chul Kee, 1986-1991 (Box 9, Folder 4)
          - Augustinus Kermite, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 19)
          - Frederik Jan Kouttjie, 1982-1986 (Box 8, Folder 32)
          - David Kosasih, 1985-1987 (Box 21, Folder 21)
          - Kwon Ho Kyung, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
          - Lalsangliana, 986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 22)
          - Andreas P. Lambe, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
          - Ferdinand Croen Lewier, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 23)
          - Teo Geok Lian, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 24)
          - Lal Liani, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 25)
          - Darwis Luke, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 26)
          - Kenmenard P. Marak, 1984-1986 (Box 21, Folder 26)
          - Christopher Sang Maung, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 27)
          - Kathryn Ann McKenzie, 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
          - Lee Chang Mee, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
          - Usman Meliala, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 28)
          - Margrate Milton Jacob, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 12)
          - Teseng Momin, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 29)
          - Risom Ngaranmi, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 30)
          - Za Tuah Ngur, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 34)
          - Maung Pye Nyein, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 13)
          - Henry Paul, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 39)
          - Stephen Paly, 1992-1994 (Box 9, Folder 29)
          - Finny Philip, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 35)
          - Somporn Pongudom, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 27)
          - Somporn Pongudom, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 28)
          - Andrews Prasad, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 31)
          - Felix Premawardhana, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 33)
          - Carmelita Kabita Ratna, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 21)
          - Priyanthi Kadirgamar, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
          - Thawng Lian Khup, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 30)
          - Joshua Ratnam, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 44)
          - John Mohan Razu, 1987-1991 (Box 8, Folder 43)
          - Helen Reala, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 37)
          - Nazarius Rumpak, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
          - John Cuai Sang, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 42)
          - K. Shanpru, 1981-1984 (Box 8, Folder 45)
          - Lee Sang-Youn, 1987-1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
          - Chandanie Senerath, 1992-1993 (Box 8, Folder 23)
          - Chan Beng Seng, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 22)
          - Almoos Sherazi, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
          - Fanindra Lal Singh, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 32)
          - Sabar Simamora, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
          - John Barathi Soundararajan, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 33)
          - Thedupa Swuro, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 34)
          - Pradit Takerngrangsarit, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 20)
          - Borong Tarigan, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 35)
          - P. Tevaraji, 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
          - L. Thungchemo, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 36)
          - Samuel Thomas Varghese, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 37)
          - Albert Walters, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 14)
          - Ging Chai Wong, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 36)
          - Chi Yuan An, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 24)
          - Christopher Yesudhas, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 38)
          - Obed Nazia Yusaf, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 16)
          - Peter Zohmingthanga, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 18)
          - Philippine team visit Pakistan and South Korea, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Asia Ecumenical Academy
        - Asia Ecumenical Academy, Bangkok, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 16)
        - Asia Ecumenical Academy, Chiang Mai, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 17)
        - Asia Ecumenical Academy, Chiang Mai, 2005 (Box 78, Folder 18)
      - Programme Committee for Education
        - Minutes, reports, 1982-1986 (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - Conferences, Consultations, Workshops
      - Parish to Parish Life Conference, 17 June-24 July 1966, Philippines. (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Asian Christian Social Scientists Conference, 1-7 Oct. 1967, Gotemba, Japan. (Box 9, Folder 36)
      - Course for church leaders from Africa, Asia and Latin America on the education and training of lay people for their tasks in the world, Feb. to May 1968. Report (Box 9, Folder 37)
      - CELT Consultation on Witness of the Laity,10-20 Apr. 1969, Perth, Australia. (Box 9, Folder 38)
      - Regional Workshop for Educators, 20-25 Oct.1973, Y.W.C.A., Madras, India. (Box 9, Folder 39)
      - Consultation on Education for Liberation and Community, 21-24 Feb.1975, Ambassador Hotel, Singapore. (Box 9, Folder 40)
      - Seminar on Non- Formal Education( Called by the Bishop of Colombo), 18-21 July.1975, Colombo, Sri Lanka. (Box 9, Folder 41)
      - Christian Education Workers Consultation, 7-11 Sept.1976, Singapore. (Box 9, Folder 42)
      - Christian Education Workers Consultation, 7-11 Sept.1976, Singapore. Situation report. (Box 9, Folder 43)
      - Consultation on Family Life on Emerging Asian Challenge, 2-9 Dec.1982, Manang, Indonesia. (Box 9, Folder 44)
      - Consultation on Family Life on Emerging Asian Challenge, 2-9 Dec.1982, Manang, Indonesia. (Box 9, Folder 45)
      - Education Education Conference, 2-7 Nov.1986, Chiang Mai, Thailand. (Box 9, Folder 45A)
      - Consultation on Integrating Spirituality with Shalom in the Local Congregation,15-21 Sept.1994, Dhaka ,Bangladesh. (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Workshop on Life and Worship in the Local Congregation, 13-20 Feb.1995, Yangon, Myanmar. (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Consultation on Christian Education in a Pluralistic Context, 22-29 Nov.1995, Yogyakarta, Indonesia. (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Consultation on Christian Education in a Pluralistic Context, 22-29 Nov.1995, Yogyakarta, Indonesia. (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Consultation on Christian Education in a Pluralistic Context, 22-29 Nov.1995, Yogyakarta, Indonesia. (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Consultation on Christian Education in a Pluralistic Context, 22-29 Nov.1995, Yogyakarta, Indonesia. (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence re." Towards an Asian Theology of Hope: Reading the Bible with New Eyes', 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Consultation on Education For JPIC, 26 Aug.-2 Sept.1996, New Mexico. (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - Consultation on Education For JPIC, 26 Aug.-2 Sept.1996, New Mexico. (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - Asia Formation Course, 2-27 Nov.1996, Cebu, Philippines. (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - Asia Formation Course, 4-29 Apr.1998, Cebu, Philippines. (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - Workshop on Worship and Curriculum .. in the Context of Asian Plurality, Bali, 1999 Oct (Box 78, Folder 10)
      - Workshop on Worship and Curriculum .. in the Context of Asian Plurality, Bali, 1999 Oct (Box 78, Folder 11)
      - Workshop on Worship and Curriculum .. in the Context of Asian Plurality, Bali, 1999 Oct (Box 78, Folder 12)
      - CCA-FABC Joint Ecumenical Formation, Taiwan, 2002 (Box 78, Folder 15)
    - Related Organizations
      - Association Of Christian Institutes for Social Concern in Asia (ACISCA)
        - Correspondence with ACISCA, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 12)
        - Correspondence with ACISCA, 1971-1976 (Box 10, Folder 13)
        - ACISCA/EACC staff training course. Korea, 1971 (Box 10, Folder 14)
        - Historical notes, constitution of ACISCA, 1969-1972 (Box 10, Folder 15)
        - Consultation on Quadrennial General Meeting,15-17 Oct.1974, Hong Kong. (Box 10, Folder 16)
        - Financial statement, 1970-1974,1976-1978 (Box 10, Folder 17)
        - Orientation programme "Movement Of Social Concern in Asia", 1973 (Box 10, Folder 18)
        - Report of the secretary submitted to the ACISCA executive committee on the 14th June 1973, Singapore. (Box 10, Folder 19)
        - Minutes of meetings, 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
        - Conference on Asian Trends, 26 Sept.-2 Oct.1976, Oiso, Japan. (Box 10, Folder 21)
        - Course for leaders of society, 1-28 Aug.1977, Jawa Barat, Indonesia (Box 10, Folder 22)
        - Asian course on Christian Vigilance, 20 Aug.-18 Sept.1977, Jawa Barat, Indonesia. (Box 10, Folder 23)
        - Correspondence with ACISCA, 1980-1983 (Box 10, Folder 24)
        - Correspondence with ACISCA, 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 25)
        - 7th General Assembly, Dhyana Pura Beach Hotel, Bali, Indonesia. August 22-28,1994 (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - CISRC-WCSRC
        - CISRC-WCSRC joint programme, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 27)
      - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia (ACUCA)
        - Circular letters, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 28)
        - ACUCA consultation on teaching science to non-science Majors,14-21 Feb.1982. Chiang Mai, Thailand. (Box 10, Folder 28A)
      - National Council of Churches in the Philippines
        - Ecumenical leadership seminar,4-10 Jan.1975, Manila, Philippines. (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - World Council of Churches/ Education and Renewal
        - Meeting of the regional educational secretaries., 1976,1977 (Box 11, Folder 2)
        - Working groups meeting, 18-26 Apr.1985, Oaxtapec, Mexico. (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - Consultation on Education and Ecumenical Formation,19-24 June 1998, Hauno, Finland. (Box 11, Folder 4)
        - WCC/WCCE the final report of the joint study commission on education 1964-1968. (Box 11, Folder 4A)
        - WCCE Proposal research project on christian education among people with an animistic background., 1970 (Box 11, Folder 4B)
    - Collected Materials
      - Publications
        - aec newsletter issue 1-4, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
        - Participants' writhing about AEC, undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
        - Asian Ecumenical Centre Newsletter No.2-4, 1976 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - Correspondence re. CCA news, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 8)
        - Education Bulletin, 1990 July, 1991 January (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Miscellaneous
        - How people learn and grow in the Christian faith by W.R. Niblett., 1964 (Box 11, Folder 10)
        - Some implications for adult Christian education of the World Council of Churches study of "Missionary Structures", undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
        - Papers from seminars, 1970-1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
        - Spiritual- Alternative lifestyle., undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
        - An appraisal of the Protestant Christian effort in higher education in Asia. Hong Kong,Thailand,Taiwan., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 15)
        - An appraisal of the Protestant Christian effort in higher education in Asia. India., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 16)
        - An appraisal of the Protestant Christian effort in higher education in Asia. Korea,Pakistan., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 17)
        - An appraisal of the Protestant Christian effort in higher education in Asia. Malaysia and Singapore,Indonesia., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 18)
        - An appraisal of the Protestant Christian effort in higher education in Asia. Philippines., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 19)
        - Laymen abroad in Christian mission. Final report submitted by Ian Thomson., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 20)
        - Rapid growth of the church in Java by Barbara Howell., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 21)
        - An appraisal of the Protestant Christian effort in higher education in Asia. Introduction., 1968 (Box 11, Folder 14)
        - Consultation on education for change. Sydney, Australia., 1971 (Box 11, Folder 22)
        - Sri Lanka SCM national workshop on education. June 1974. Pilimalalawa (Box 11, Folder 23)
        - Minutes of the sixth meeting of the World Collaboration committee for Christian Lay Centre, Academies and Movements for Social Concern., 1980 (Box 11, Folder 23A)
        - Miscellaneous papers., 1966-1976 (Box 11, Folder 24)
        - Miscellaneous papers., 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 25)
        - Miscellaneous papers., 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Faith, Mission and Unity
    The Faith, Mission, and Unity program desk subsumed the Urban Rural Mission desk at the time of CCA's restructuring in 2000.
    - Administrative records
      - Correspondence, Australia, 2001-2002 (Box 160, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, general (1 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box 160, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, general (2 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box 160, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, general (3 of 3), 1999-2000 (Box 160, Folder 4)
      - FMU financial reports, 1999-2005 (Box 160, Folder 5)
      - FMU Program plan and quarterly reports, 2001-2006 (Box 160, Folder 6)
      - FMU General Committee report and strategic planning; Leadership capacity building in Bangladesh, 2001-2004 (Box 160, Folder 7)
      - Misc. papers incl. project reports, activities planning, 2000-2001 (Box 160, Folder 8)
      - Program, Innabuyog-Metro Baguio, Philippines, 2001-2002 (Box 160, Folder 9)
      - Malaysia reports and correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 160, Folder 10)
      - Myanmar reports and correspondence, 2002-2005 (Box 160, Folder 11)
      - Pakistan reports and correspondence, 2000-2004 (Box 160, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Michael Earle, Conference of Churches in Aotearoa New Zealand criticizing FMU program, 2003 (Box 160, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence and Staff Records
      - Josef P. Widyatmadja
        - Correspondence, general, 2000 January-June (Box 160, Folder 14)
        - Correspondence re. URM activities planning, 2001-2005 (Box 160, Folder 15)
        - Correspondence re. Philippines visit incl. misc. URM reports, 1999-2000 (Box 160, Folder 16)
        - URM miscellaneous reports and correspondence, 2001-2005 (Box 160, Folder 17)
        - URM miscellaneous reports and correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 160, Folder 18)
        - CCA/FMU Consultation Affirming Fullness of Life in the Context of Migrant Workers' Struggles, 10-15 Nov., 2003, Taiwan (Box 160, Folder 19)
    - Program Activities and Conferences
      - CCA-URM/CCC Forum on Spirituality, Cultural Development and Globalization in Asia, 3-9 Dec., 2001, Shanghai-Nanjing (Box 160, Folder 20)
      - Congress of Asian Theologians, 4-10 Aug., 2003, Chiang Mai (Box 160, Folder 21)
      - Consultation on the Role of Churches in Caring for and Protecting Undocumented Children in South East Asia, 1-4 Sept., 2004, Penang (Box 160, Folder 22)
      - Ecumenical Enablers' Program, 4-9 Sept., 2000, Bangkok (Box 160, Folder 23)
      - Ecumenical Enablers' Program, 11-16 Mar., 2002, Bangkok (Box 160, Folder 24)
      - WCC Asia Regional Group Meeting, 1990, 1992 (Box 160, Folder 25)
  - Interchurch Aid for Mission and Services
    - Advisory Committee meeting minutes and reports, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Advisory Committee meeting minutes and reports, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - Annual report, 1968 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1969 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1974 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Financial reports, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Interchurch Aid Committee meeting minutes and reports (Creation of Asian Christian Service programme), 1969 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous papers and reports, 1962-1970 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - International Affairs
    - Administrative records
      - Asian Charter on Human Rights, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Asian Charter on Human Rights, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Asian Charter on Human Rights, 1993 (Box 27, Folder 17)
      - Asian Charter on Human Rights, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 18)
      - Asian Charter on Human Rights, 1994 (Box 27, Folder 19)
      - Asian Charter on Human Rights, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - Asian Charter on Human Rights, 1994-1996 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      - Asian Issues source material. Includes 5 1/4 inch floppy disk., 1989 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      - Asian Issues source material re. Malaysia and Nepal., 1989 (Box 28, Folder 4)
      - Asian Issues source material for issue on children in war, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 5)
      - Asian Issues source material for issue on children in war, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 6)
      - Asian Issues source material for issue on children in war, 1993 (Box 28, Folder 7)
      - Audited reports of income and expenditure, 1983-1991 (Box 28, Folder 8)
      - CCA Communications desk, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
      - CCA directory, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 10)
      - CCA visit to Europe, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 11)
      - CCA IA contact with Socialist States working group, 1986-1987 (Box 28, Folder 12)
      - CCA IA involvement in the Asian Human Rights Commission and the Asian Legal Resource Center, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 13)
      - CCA and relationship with China, 1992-1994 (Box 99, Folder 39)
      - CCA WSCF joint programme, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 14)
      - Committee minutes, administrative budget, and reports, 1983-1984 (Box 28, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence re. Indonesia and prisoners, 1972-1976 (Box 28, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence re. China seminar, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence re. interactions with China, 1978-1980 (Box 99, Folder 37)
      - Correspondence, reports re. interactions with China, 1983-1987 (Box 99, Folder 38)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous including Advisory Committee on International Affairs meeting minutes, 1978-1980 (Box 28, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence miscellaneous, 1979, 1983, 1990, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence re. Asian Issues publication, 1980-1986 (Box 28, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence re. publications and Asian Issues mailing list, 1980-1991 (Box 28, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Law Association for Asia the Pacific. Includes Human Rights Bulletin., 1981-1989 (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence re. Human Rights Fund, 1982-1987 (Box 29, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence re. communication, 1983-1986, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence re. funding request for Regional Council on Human Rights in Asia meeting, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous includes papers about labor laws in Asia from unknown conference., 1983 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence re. Asian Human Rights Commission and Asian Human Rights Symposium, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence re. the creation of the Asian Human Rights commission and Asian Legal Resource Centre, incl. reports., 1984 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence re. human response to the justice and peace issues in the Sri Lanka context, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence re. possible publication on history of press legislation in India, Pakistan, and Sri Lanka., 1984 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Switzerland, 1984-1986 (Box 29, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, Australia, 1984-1988 (Box 29, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1984-1988 (Box 29, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence, Clement John's outgoing letters, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence re. Irian Jaya, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1985 (Box 29, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1985-1986 (Box 29, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence re. Asia Latin American exchange visits on human rights, 1986 (Box 29, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Church of Sweden Mission, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence re. Jose Ma. Sison's visit to India, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence, National Council of Churches in Japan and Korea, 1986-1992 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence re. program projects and direction, 1986-1987 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, Tremewan, Chris, 1986-1991 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, Asian Student Association, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Ecumenical Peace Program in Asia, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence re. Human Rights Sunday, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence re. Korean lawyers visit to Philippines, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence re. WCC-CCA Asia/Latin America Exchange visit, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence, New Zealand, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Correspondence, Taiwan, 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Correspondence re. Case study publications on CCA Singapore expulsion, Nuclear Free Nation: a case study of Aotearo/New Zealand, and Human Rights in Sri Lanka, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Correspondence re. CCA delegation to China, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, Nepal including newsletter Fodenu, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence re. CCIA Human Rights Advocacy group meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, re. CCA staff meeting, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence re. Christian Peace Conference, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, Ecumenical Peace Program in Asia, 1988-1990 (Box 30, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence re. Ecumenical Solidarity Support includes minutes and reports, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 23)
      - Correspondence re. foreign policy, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, Japan CCA office, miscellaneous, Esther Byu, and Kenichi Otsu, 1988-1992 (Box 30, Folder 25)
      - Correspondence, Japan CCA office: Kenichi Otsu, Godwin R. Singh, and Pura Calo, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence of Mary Kay Hobbs (staff member in charge of EPPIA), 1987-1989 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence re. NCC of Korea's International Christian Consultation on "Justice and Peace in Korea", 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, re. theological reflection paper with Harvey Perkins, 1988-1989 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence with CCA Youth desk secretary, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Correspondence, India A-B, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Correspondence, India C-D, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Correspondence, India E-Z, 1988-1992 (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence, Bangladesh and Burma, 1989-1992 (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Correspondence re. case filed by Mr. Lee Kuan Yew against "Far Eastern Econo-Review", 1989 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Correspondence re. Clement John's participation in WCC Ecumenical Human Rights meeting in Quito, Ecuador, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence, Democracy and Peace in Asia, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Correspondence, Free Legal Assistance Group (FLAG) Human Rights Foundation. Includes reports and pamphlet Know Your Human Rights., 1989-1991 (Box 31, Folder 13)